After comparing running time and accuracy, we decide to use features selected from IG plus these three additional features.

Besides, we have to put weight on different tokens. We could just directly use frequency matrix, but it might introduce some bias. In industry, people always view TF-IDF as an applicable resolution. Since we are doing sentiment analysis here, many experts suggest that boolean weight might be more accurate. 

The models we use now are Linear regression and Naive Bayes.

After split the data into training and testing, we get the following results. 

To improve the performance, in the future we want to try word2vec, put more efforts on tuning hyperparameters and try more complicated models.

